Herzog, Paul M. Papers 5847
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Paul M. Herzog Papers
1937-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Herzog, Paul M.
5847
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers.
5713671
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files 5252: Arthur Meyer Papers 5318: NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5435 OH: NLRB Oral History Project Miscellaneous 5588: David L. Cole Papers 5619: ACWA Records 6037 P: Labor Leaders and Subjects Photographs 6058 OH: Kheel Center Collection of Oral Histories
Herzog, Paul M., 1906-1986
5713671
- Paul M. Herzog Newspaper Clippings, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Scrap Book
- Diary NLRB, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Diary, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Diary, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- National Diary, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Manhattan Daily Journal, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Standard Daily Journal, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Continental Diary, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- PMH Speeches, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Binder
- PMH Speeches, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Speeches by PMH, AAA Period, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- NY State Labor Relations Board, 1940-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- NLRB, Appointment, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- NLRB, Congressional Testimony by PMH, 1945-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NLRB, Re-Appointment, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Speeches by PMH, 1937-1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  SLRB & NLRB
- NLRB, since 1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Upholsterers Union Review Board, 1953-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- PMH Speeches, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- AAA, Management Consultants' Report, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- AAA, Resignation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- International Labour Office, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- AAA, Appointment, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The National Board (Box 2, Folder 16)
- La Vraie Revolution de Roosevelt (Box 2, Folder 17)
  French Book